I got there at the right moment in fact the timing was almost perfect
damn it I'm sorry Luke Wong this is against the rules but I don't know what else to do
I was about to alter the past she's getting away but then I realized there was something I couldn't
change I'm impulsive and reckless I wasn't sure how things were going to play out so I settled on a new
goal catch Li Tianxin and no matter what don't let Luke Wong go with him
at that moment I felt something strange
before I knew it I was out of the photo back here
well that was quick what did you figure out where did Luke Wong and Li Tianxin end up
I just got kicked out of the photo how the hell did that happen
you were forced out yeah the same as before
whatever sent me back it wasn't my choice
it was after physical contact both times
yes I've been going through this footage and may hold answers
when Wang Juan took you away Li Tianxin was holding both of your hands
it's probably safe to assume that his ability to control others is somehow dependent on physical contact
I'm tired of people looking at me and seeing a freak when I'm just trying to survive
I'm sorry I don't think you're a freak
you're honestly sorry then you should make it up to me
what was that speak up
one more time I said
I would answer at least a few questions like why Wang Juan led you out of the station
how she ended up handcuffed to a pipe it wasn't her
how did I get here
Chang Joesha
there is still something that doesn't add up though
he'd have to be close to someone in order to touch them
but sometimes it's remote how does he pull that off
I think I might know
she has a power too not just him
here look she relies on photos
that's how she's able to see inside of a person's head
I'm pretty sure it works like this
she can use a picture to know what someone is doing and even take a peek at their memories
but she doesn't become that person
that would track
he knew I was lying when I faced him
I told you not to lie
see you can fool me
but she sees right through you
he said I couldn't fool her
she was inside of your head
and you knew the truth
they cooperate and use their abilities together like me and Lu Guang
so they can possess someone with a picture
that's why he was after me
he told me as much
talk about a convenient power
I think I might take it
see what kind of trouble I can get into
you can do that
with my ability he could return to the past
control somebody and change history however he wanted
if Lu hadn't stepped in
we have to figure out where he is
the half-dead idiot is bleeding out all over the floor
and I don't want to deal with the corpse
we need a way to bring Cheng Xiaoxiao here
here
he's the only thing that matters
once we have him
we can rewrite all of it
even finding that sister of yours
here
Shiji we're gonna have dinner
come here and take a quick nap
here we go
let's head out
coming?
yeah of course
stay close
eyes open
don't mess this up
I won't
there you are
get what we need?
hello
so wild saying hi to you like this
kind of a trip
the man's got a baby on the way
what a shame
you are
love
shiji
ever
something like that
you are
shiji
er Keo
is
far
ablast
and
dr
Worthy
but
creation
oh
god
Hey boss, something wrong? Should we chase him?
You check in with Ma. I don't want problems.
I never thought she'd run off on you, or that you'd lose her.
It's a pity. I can't abide betrayal, even from her. She is beyond mercy now.
That can't be our only option.
That depends. What would you suggest? What's our new endgame?
Will you help us? We're trying to find our friend.
Please look, I know what you can do, so use this to see where he is.
What a clever little brain you have. It's why you're a good partner.
You're Li Qian Chen, right?
So why don't you be a good partner to me, and tell me how you knew the when and where of our plan?
Why would I do that? He'll just kill me once I do.
Maybe, maybe not.
It's always smart to hold on to your trump card.
That's so. Sounds like you're getting desperate to me.
And now you've gone and made me angry.
And I don't want to be nice anymore.
Now, let's see. How close do I want to bring you to death?
To death.
Find him? Is he hurt?
What's happening? Where is he? Is he in pain?
Stay calm!
Hey, hey!
You're alright.
Focus. Is Lu Guang okay?
Hmm. The bleeding's stopped for now.
You should survive.
What do you want from me?
Relax. You'll see. Get changed. You're almost on.
Almost on.
Over here!
Just now, the brother called from a blocked number. He said he'll give us Lu Guang in exchange for you.
In my experience, police want lots of manpower and prep time for hostage trades. They'll pull tricks. Like dressing an officer up as your target to pull a fast one on you. The best way to avoid this is to give them a tight deadline so they don't have time to think.
This has to go down at 3am. If we bail, Lu Guang won't be safe. That's 35 minutes from now. It'll take you at least 20 to get there.
I've currently got men interrogating Wang's attackers. As well as a few others who are tracking Chen Jin.
Xiao Li won't have the luxury of reparation. Backup will have to wait for later.
Even if he gets any bright ideas, I've got sharp eyes outside of the police station.
We don't want Xiao Li escorting Cheng Xiaoshu. I have someone else in mind.
Only two people can go in. You and…
I still feel that slap. I must say it stings.
Xiao Ling.
Right. I'm in.
I'm in.
Slow down. Be smart. We'll think of another way.
There's no time to argue. Let's go. Plan on the drive.
Backup's coming. Prop the door. Keep it open.
Keep it open.
welcome honored guests our special show is about to begin step inside the theater and take your
places i'm afraid you'll have to leave your belongings out here mr chung has a poor track record after
all don't worry i have costumes for the two of you please change quickly you don't want to miss the
curtain he's two steps ahead of us you there everyone in place yes sir ready to move on your signal
ah you can leave your stuff anywhere then step through security again
okay that's that we can't monitor them now so it's up to you watch over them
please not so fast
it's important that you follow the rules of the show even if they seem strict
that's the only way to guarantee against injury
shall we begin walking towards each other slowly
did you not hear i said to start walking towards each other both of you
very good take his place in the spotlight
don't worry i got this
bravo well done
are you okay
now for the curtain call
wave goodbye to your audience
where'd he go
captain
i've got the guang
feels like our first real meeting
no photos here no way for you to cheat in this fight
time to move
catch li tianchen and chenjin
not bad
your plan actually worked
why aren't the others here yet
we just spoke on the phone
they'll be out soon
see them
how close are they to the entrance
oh shit
stay put
don't leave the car
captain chu
hi there
it's a pleasure to see you again
don't try to pull any more stunts okay
hug humming with me
you